photofacefun.com 2015-12-28

# Photofacefun.com

For users who are concerning about intellectual property right loss of pictures uploaded to our website: You retain all intellectual property rights on all pictures uploaded to PhotoFaceFun.com We do not intend to take the mentioned rights, it remains yours.

All processed pictures are private by default and are not visible to other users. All uploaded pictures are deleted from PhotoFaceFun.com in 3 days.

PhotoFaceFun respects your confidentiality is working hard for securing your private information. We want you to understand how we can gather, store, use and secure any private information. We will not transfer any information to 3rd parties, except for the one mentioned in the actual Privacy Policy. By uploading a picture to our web-site in order to use our services, you accept our Privacy Policy.

We can change this policy at any time with a prior notification. We will post the notification of a new edition of the policy on our web-site; updated policy will be in an effect immediately. Our web-site [http://www.PhotoFaceFun.com](http://www.photofacefun.com/), software and services will be refered as a ”Service” in this Privacy Policy. Please, pay attention that this Privacy Policy does not cover information that is gathered through other ways, besides the use of the services (also in the standalone mode) or from various sources.

**1) What kind of information do we gather?**

The service gathers the information from you when you enter our web-site or upload a picture.

As many web-sites, we use cookies for gathering the information on visitors as well as tracking visits of our web-site. Please, refer to “Are we using cookies?” that is below for getting further information on cookies and on how we use them.

**2) What do we use you information for?**

Any information that we gather from you can be used in one of the following ways:

For personalizing user experience (Your information helps us to react upon your individual needs more efficiently

For the web-site improvement (We continuously try to improve the offers of our web-site based on the information and feedback that we receive from you)

For the increase of the quality of the servicing of clients (Your information can help us to react more efficiently on queries of the servicing of clients and demands in support)

For the sending of periodic e-mail newsletters. Email address can be used for sending information concerning your order and a query, company news, offers, technical information, etc.

For making competitions, career promotions, surveys and other functionalities of the web-site

**3) Are we using cookies?**

Yes. Cookies are small files that the web-site sends to the hard drive of your computer through a web-browser (if you permit); that makes the web-site to determine your browser version and remember certain information.

**4) Are we disclosing any information to 3 rd parties?**

We are not transferring or disclosing your private information to any 3rd parties. This does not concern trusted 3rd parties that help us with the work of the web-site, our business and servicing you as long as those parties agree on keeping that information confidential.

We can disclose your information when we think that it is needed by the law, the policy of the web-site  and defending rights, property and security us and 3rd parties. However, private information of visitors cannot be transferred to 3rd parties for marketing, advertising or other goals.

We value your confidentiality; we have made all needed security measures that we can correspond to California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance. That is why we will not distribute your private information to 3rd parties without your acceptance.

According to California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance, all users of the web-site can change their private data at any moment. For doing this, you can contact us through a web-page available at the address [http://www.PhotoFaceFun.com/contact/](http://www.photofacefun.com/contact/)

**5) CAN-SPAM Act of 2003**

We have made all needed measures for ensuring that we correspond to CAN-SPAM Act of 2003 and never distribute unclear and misleading information.

**6) Your acceptance**

By using our web-site you agree to our Privacy Policy. The changing of the Privacy Policy, if we decide to change the Privacy Policy, we will publish changes on this page and/or update the date of changes  of the Privacy Policy below. Changes of the Privacy Policy will only affect information that is gathered after its adoption.

**7) Intellectual Property rights**

The web-site uses pictures and other materials made by us or by other authors without violations of the Creative Commons license. All 3rd party pictures can be freely found on the internet and are not used for commercial purposes.

If you are an author of the picture and do not want that PhotoFaceFun uses it, contact us through a web-page at the address [http://www.PhotoFaceFun.com/contact/](http://www.photofacefun.com/contact/)

**8) Feedback**

If you have any question concerning this Privacy Policy, you can contact us through a web-page at the address [http://www.PhotoFaceFun.com/contact/](http://www.photofacefun.com/contact/)

**9) Guaranty of users confidentiality**

We guaranty to you, our client that we have made all deliberated efforts to make our Privacy Policy corresponding to the following important laws and confidentiality initiatives:

California Online Privacy Protection Act

Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act

Privacy Alliance

Controlling the Assault of Non-Solicited Pornography and Marketing Act
